You still remember Wei Xiaodong, right?
Wei Xiaodong.
This child died too tragically.
I looked into the case from back then.
Because of the Wei Xiaodong case,
you suffered a lot.
Wei Xiaodong, male, 12 years old.
He had multiple bruises on his body from being beaten.
There were two parallel stab wounds on his abdomen
with opposite blade surfaces.
It was suspected that the deceased suffered abuse before death.
During the struggle,
the victim was stabbed by the killer,
resulting in death.
Moreover, the victim's lower body was severely torn.
It's possible they were tortured and killed by a pedophile,
then dumped.
Chief,
I request to open an investigation immediately.
The nature of this case is extremely heinous.
We must investigate it thoroughly
and catch the real killer.
Sir.
Chief.
The victim was found in our jurisdiction.
I request to participate in the investigation.
Detective Li,
I think you just want to steal the credit.
You two
are only good for catching thieves.
You can't solve this case without me.
You!
Chengrui,
Jinwen,
you two
will assist Jiang Siyao.
Yes, sir.
Wei Xiaodong is an orphan.
He was previously adopted by a rickshaw puller, Li Youcai.
Now, as long as we find Li Youcai,
we will have clues.
Got it.
Enemies really do cross paths.
You're a step late.
Reaction speed is also an ability.
Take him away.
Li Chengrui has been a police officer for ten years longer than you.
It's natural that he has more experience.
Don't be discouraged.
You take it well.
Officer.
I did adopt Xiaodong.
But this child,
he didn't have enough to eat or wear with me.
He ran away on his own in less than two months.
Li Youcai.
We've already checked your background.
At your age,
you don't have a wife,
and can't even feed yourself.
Why would you raise a child?
Speak.
Have you been a bachelor for so long
that you've become a psychopath?
Officer.
I swear to God.
I just wanted to adopt a child
to look after me in my old age.
But who would have thought this child
would be so heartless?
He ran away on his own.
You won't talk, huh?
Then we'll have to use torture.
Superintendent Li.
Old Li.
Without conclusive evidence,
beating someone indiscriminately,
if it gets to the chief,
it won't be easy to explain.
Don't you think so?
They're out.
You three
and Li Youcai are all from the rickshaw company.
We can prove
that Xiaodong ran away two months ago.
Yes, officer.
Youcai is really an honest man.
For so many years,
he has never quarreled with anyone.
That's right.
He lives with us.
He couldn't possibly do such a thing.
Yeah.
Do you know
after Wei Xiaodong ran away,
where he went?
We are not quite sure about that.
You three,
please go and ask around too.
Come to us anytime if you have any clues.
Deputy Director,
I request the immediate release of Li Youcai.
He couldn't possibly be the murderer.
How do you know Li Youcai is not the real murderer?
All the rickshaw pullers at the company
can prove that what Li Youcai said is true.
How do you know they are not accomplices
or just covering for him?
When Wei Xiaodong was found,
apart from the scars,
he was very clean.
He couldn't possibly have died in such a dirty place as the rickshaw company.
All right.
Release Li Youcai,
and keep investigating.
Yes, sir.
What's wrong, Old Xu?
Officer Jiang,
we found something.
Found what?
Yesterday, we searched the whole city.
A street vendor said
Xiaodong
was taken away by
a slightly older boy.
What boy?
About 15 or 16 years old,
tall and thin.
The vendor didn't see his face clearly.
Later, we asked around privately.
A fisherman by the Haihe River said
there's a teenager named Hu Agen
living alone by the river.
A couple of days ago,
a boy stayed with him.
Okay, got it.
You guys go back first.
What are you doing?
What's your name?
Agen.
Full name.
Hu Agen.
I...
I didn't break the law.
You...
What are you doing?
Take a look.
This dagger of yours,
its blade perfectly matches
the wounds on Wei Xiaodong's body.
What else do you have to say?
I don't even know what you're talking about.
A few days ago,
a 12-year-old boy
was staying at your house.
Who is he to you?
A friend.
What kind of friend?
Just a friend
I met by chance who shares my interests.
But officer,
I really don't know his name.
More like shared sexual interests.
What do you mean?
Hu Agen.
The evidence is conclusive.
You killed Wei Xiaodong.
What else is there to deny?
I didn't.
You're talking nonsense.
Shut up.
How dare you still deny it.
Torture him.
Wait a minute.
Come out with me.
Get out. It wasn't me. You...
Do you have any idea
what you are doing?
I know exactly what I'm doing.
It's none of your business.
I know you hate this kind of crime,
but until the evidence comes out,
we can't determine if he's the killer.
Why are you acting like Li Chengrui?
The murder weapon has been found.
We have both witnesses and material evidence.
Lin Jinwen.
What exactly do you know,
or who are you protecting?
I don't know anything,
nor am I protecting anyone.
I just don't want you to insult him like this.
You...
I was wrong about yesterday.
I apologize to you.
Using torture during interrogation,
isn't that normal?
That was normal procedure.
Did you have to get so mad?
I just went to check.
The person who stayed at Hu Agen's place a couple of days ago
wasn't Wei Xiaodong at all.
Hu Agen was telling the truth.
Officer Lin!
Officer Lin, bad news!
Hu Agen committed suicide in prison.
His parents are carrying his body
and making a scene at the police station entrance.
Hurry up.
Jiang Siyao,
come out here!
Give me back my son!
People like her don't deserve to be cops.
A murderer with no regard for human life!
She's the one who killed my son!
Tell Jiang Siyao to come out right now!
Folks, please calm down.
Tell her to come out!
Everyone, listen to me.
Right, making a rash judgment based on a single weapon.
Some top female detective of Fenghuang Street.
If you ask me,
she's the top female psycho of Fenghuang Street.
Did my son die for nothing?
Li Chengrui,
you better watch your mouth.
Am I wrong?
If she hadn't tried to be smart with this case,
would it have come to this?
Why are you protecting her so much?
Could it be
you want to be a live-in son-in-law at the Jiang Mansion?
Say that again if you dare.
Calm down.
Chief.
It's my fault.
I'll resign to take the blame.
Ayao.
I brought you into this profession,
and you are my last student.
I understand how you feel.
But,
you can't act on impulse.
I didn't expect it to end like this.
I've read the file.
You followed the procedure completely.
Why did Hu Agen commit suicide?
Don't you want to know?
Who exactly killed Wei Xiaodong?
Sir.
After three days of detention,
if there was no evidence,
we would have let Hu Agen go.
Why couldn't he even hold on
for one day before committing suicide?
There's still a lot you can do.
I hope you can pull yourself together,
find out the truth,
instead of running away.
So...
The case from back then
was never closed.
Just like what Senior Song and I found out
about the banned drug, Seven-Colored Krait,
this case
came to an abrupt end here.
The Seven-Colored Krait case,
the Wei Xiaodong case,
and the Jingxiang Society case.
Between all of these,
what exactly is the connection?
Don't you think
the clues provided by this mysterious person
are pointing to something specific?
In the pile of bones in the suburbs of the capital,
the banned drug Seven-Colored Krait was found.
Peter used the Seven-Colored Krait drug
to rape and murder young boys.
Then the missing girls
were locked up and indoctrinated by the Jingxiang Society.
The master of the Jingxiang Society
is Lin Yousheng, who killed John years ago.
John and Peter were both members of the church.
It seems like everything goes around in circles
and comes back to the starting point.
Such a serious case
hasn't been solved for over a decade
because every time it reaches a critical point,
it encounters strong resistance.
Now the whole city
is paying attention to this case.
The mysterious person probably wants to
use this attention
to create huge public pressure,
so that this case
can't be easily suppressed anymore.
Perhaps,
the Jingxiang Society is a crucial step in his plan.
Boss.
Damn it.
How is he?
He's dead.
Things were just getting clear.
Now it's a mess again.
Who do you think
killed the boss?
Someone who doesn't want us to solve the case.
It seems
he wants to cut off this clue.
Another life lost.
Superintendent Li,
you always show up right on time.
Sorry.
I'm a step late again.
Reporters,
the Jingxiang Society incident
is credited to our Phoenix Police Department.
But this case
is not over yet,
because the mastermind has not been found.
We will do our best
to find the real culprit.
Inspector Jiang,
do you mean
Venerable Jiaohua is not the main culprit,
and the killer is someone else?
Inspector Jiang, please tell us more.
I have one more thing to announce.
I formally apologize to the victims
of the Wei Xiaodong case.
It has remained unsolved for five years
due to my
dereliction of duty.
Through our investigation,
the pile of bones case in the capital suburbs,
the smuggling case of Peter, a church doctor in the British Concession,
the rape and murder of a young boy,
and the abduction of women by the Jingxiang Society
are all related to the incident five years ago.
I announce that
starting today,
the investigation into the Wei Xiaodong case will be reopened.
There is not a single wound on the deceased's body.
But from the deceased's stomach,
potassium cyanide was extracted.
Potassium cyanide.
If he really is from the Jingxiang Society,
then the clue he provided us
about the police shoes
was just to mislead our investigation.
But,
as for the master of the Jingxiang Society,
we have no clues at all right now.
This organization, the Jingxiang Society,
is far from simple.
It seems
someone is watching us all the time.
No.
Come here and take a look.
Look,
this tattoo
was done recently.